Hello, have you ever wondered how to heal a broken heart after a breakup?
This is no easy task.
But, I'm Dr. Felicia and I'm here to give you a few tips on how to do that.
For one thing you want to indulge yourself in things that you like and surround yourself by supportive family and friends who understand the situation.
The other thing you want to do is try to embellish some of the good parts of that relationship and try to make some senses to why it actually broke up.
It's really hard to be honest and look inside ourselves and say, "okay, what did I do to contribute to this breakup", if anything, maybe nothing, but, it's good for you to take a look at that and analyze it.
The other thing you want to do is also, your response may differ, whether you're, what we call an internal directed person, perhaps you think about it a lot, you're going to, you're going to internalize it, you're not going to speak to your friends, you're just kind of go and go quiet walks on the beach, process that information by yourself.
Or, you maybe what we call externally driven, where you need to throw yourself in a lot of activities and laughter and jokes.
I would strongly recommend laughter is the best medicine.
If you can get through the breakup and eventually time does heal wounds.
So that some of those raw wounds will heal in time.
Remember everyone does survive breakups and usually by the time you're in your 20's and 30's, you've already had your share of high school breakups.
So you should be somewhat condition to that process.
You will heal, you will get over this and with that in mind, remember how you go about healing from the breakup, healing your broken heart, depends on you making conscious efforts to stay active and busy.
Right?
Good luck.
Dr. Felicia here, goodbye.